Inventory of the Colby E. "Babe" Slater Collection D-394
University of California, Davis General Library, Dept. of Special Collections
- Publications, 1912-2004; Series 3; 23 folders.
  - University of California, Davis, 1917-2009; Subseries 3.1; 5 folders; 2 linear feet
    - University Farm Agricola, April 27, 1917; D394.3.1.14 (Box 6, Folder 1.14)
    - University Farm Agricola, Agricultural Section, Ninth Annual Picnic Day edition, undated; D394.3.1.15 (Box 6, Folder 1.15)
      Slater, Colby E. -- Archives; University of California, Davis -- History; University Farm Agricola; Picnic Day
    - The Calpha Bear: Agricultural Fraternity of Calpha, 1939; D394.3.1.16 (Box 1, Folder 22.1)
      Greek letter societies -- California -- Davis; Student activities -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Calpha bear; University of California, Davis. College of Agricultural and Environmental Sciences; University of California, Davis -- Alumni and alumnae
    - Calpha Bear: Agricultural Fraternity of Calpha, 1941; D394.3.1.17 (Box 1, Folder 22.2)
      Student activities -- California -- Davis; Greek letter societies -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Calpha bear; University of California, Davis. College of Agricultural and Environmental Sciences; University of California, Davis -- Alumni and alumnae
    - Calpha Bear: Agricultural Fraternity of Calpha, 1942; D394.3.1.18 (Box 1, Folder 22.3)
    - Calpha Bear: Agricultural Fraternity of Calpha, 1948; D394.3.1.19 (Box 1, Folder 22.4)
    - Calpha Bear: Agricultural Fraternity of Calpha, 1950; D394.3.1.20 (Box 1, Folder 22.5)
    - Clipping, Open letter to alumni: "Hay!" Picnic Day!, undated; D394.1.3.21 (Box 1, Folder 23.1)
      Student activities -- California -- Davis; Festivals -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis--History; Picnic Day
    - Clipping, Knight nixes invite, PD will survive, March 21, 1957; D394.3.1.22 (Box 1, Folder 23.2)
      Student activities -- California -- Davis; Festivals -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis--History; Picnic Day; Knight, Goodwin, 1896-1970
    - UCD Dimension (Fall), 1967; D394.3.1.23 (Box 1, Folder 23 A)
      Loose sheet copy of page 19.
      Slater, Colby E. -- Archives; California Aggie Alumni Association; University of California, Davis -- Alumni and alumnae
    - Clipping, Cal-Aggie alumni section, 1965; D394.3.1.24 (Box 6, Folder 2.1)
      College sports -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archives; University of California, Davis -- History; University of California, Davis -- Alumni and alumnae
    - Clipping, Aggie old-timers enjoy the harmony of old favorites at a reunion dinner in Davis, 1965; D394.3.1.25 (Box 6, Folder 2.2)
      Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History; Picnic Day
    - Clipping, Davis Enterprise (memorial award: Herb Barker (left), president of the Cal Aggie Alumni Association, is shown presenting the (Babe) Slater perpetual athletic trophy, Monday, October 25, 1965; D394.3.1.26 (Box 6, Folder 2.3)
      Two copies.
      Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History; Davis Enterprise; California Aggie Alumni Association -- History
    - Clipping, UCD students prepare welcome for first alumni homecoming arrivals, 1965; D394.3.1.27 (Box 6, Folder 2.4)
      Student activities -- California -- Davis; Festivals -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History; University of California, Davis -- Alumni and alumnae
    - Clipping, Davis prepares to welcome alumni for weekend homecoming festival, undated; D394.3.1.28 (Box 6, Folder 2.5)
      Festivals -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History; University of California, Davis -- Alumni and alumnae
    - Homecoming 1965, October 23, 1965; D394.3.1.29 (Box 6, Folder 2.6)
      College sports -- California -- Davis; Festivals -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archives; University of California, Davis -- History
    - Clippings, Colby E. "Babe" Slater Memorial Athletic Award, 1965; D394.3.1.30 (Box 6, Folder 2.7)
    - Flyer, ASUCD presents Homecoming, 1965, D394.3.1.31 (Box 6, Folder 2.8)
      Student activities -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History; University of California, Davis. Associated Students
    - Clipping, Babe Slater trophy given to Aggies, October 23, 1965; D394.3.1.32 (Box 6, Folder 2.9)
      College sports -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History
    - Clipping, UCD students prepare for homecoming events, October 23, 1965; D394.3.1.33 (Box 6, Folder 2.10)
      two copies.
      College sports -- California -- Davis; Student activities -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History; University of California, Davis -- Alumni and alumnae
    - Flyer, The Buzzsaw (Rotary Club of West Sacramento): Chips from the Buzzsaw, November 16, 1965; D394.3.1.34 (Box 6, Folder 2.11)
      College sports -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History; California Aggie Alumni Association
    - Clipping, Aggies stomp Chico State, October 1967; D394.3.1.35 (Box 6, Folder 2.12)
    - Clipping, Lynn (Pappy) Waldorf, center, coach of the University of California football team, is shown with four Yolo men who made sports history for the Golden Bears, undated; D394.3.1.36 (Box 6, Folder 2.13)
    - Clipping, Kin of Colby Slater bids for UCD stardom, October 25, 1974; D394.3.1.37 (Box 6, Folder 2.14)
    - Clipping, Top Aggie athletes, June 10, 1978; D394.3.1.38 (Box 6, Folder 2.15)
    - Clipping, At the dedication of the Veterinary Medicine Teaching and Research Center in Tulare on Oct. 7, a plaque was presented by Chancellor Meyer and Richard H. McCapes, the first director of the facility; UCD fraternity and sorority members bury a time capsule beneath the walkway north of Shields Library, 1984; D394.3.1.39 (Box 6, Folder 2.16)
      Student activities -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History
    - Two message slips from John L. Hardie, Alumni Affairs. One addressed to Mrs. Slater and one addressed to Mrs. McCapes, October 26, 1965; D394.3.1.45 (Box 6, Folder 2.17)
      Hardie, John L.; Slater, Virgina C., 1909-1991; McCapes, Marilyn Slater
    - Clippings, 'Babe' Slater, the first Aggie great, November 1972; D394.3.1.40 (Box 6, Folder 3.1)
      2 pages, plus second copy comprised of portion of first and second page (article portions only).
    - Instant replay: football program of the University of California, Davis:Boardwalk Bowl edition, December, 1972; D394.3.1.41 (Box 6, Folder 3.2)
      College sports -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archives; University of California, Davis -- History
    - Instant replay: football program of the University of California, Davis, November 11, 1972; D394.3.1.42 (Box 6, Folder 3.3)
      College sports -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis -- History; Instant replay (Davis, Calif.)
    - Instant Replay: Football Program of the University of California, Davis, December 1972; D394.3.1.43 (Box 6, Folder 3.4)
    - Clipping, 10 inducted into Ag Hall of Fame, October 11, 1980; D394.3.1.44 (Box 6, Folder 3.5)
      Original and copy. Copy comprised of two pages.
      College sports -- California -- Davis; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; University of California, Davis
    - UC Davis Sports Quarterly featuring Babe Slater, 2004; 2 linear feet (Box 9-10)
      Multiple copies
    - Book, "UC Davis Aggie Pride" featuring Babe Slater, 2009 (Box 10)
  - World War I, circa 1918; Subseries 3.2; 1 folder.
    Contains clippings.
    - Clipping, Here is Yolo County's second increment of liberty boys, September 24, 1917; D394.3.2.1 (Box 6, Folder 4.1)
      Two copies of Original (full page and individual article clippings) and photocopy (2 pages)
      World War, 1914-1918; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive
    - Clipping, What are we fighting for? Why are we still fighting?, October 4, 1918, October 8, 1918, October 12, 1918; D394.3.2.2 (Box 6, Folder 4.2)
    - Clipping, C.E. (Babe) Slater, ..., was chosen by the Yolo draft board to be captain for the next 43 men to be sent to the Army from the county, September 21, 1917; D394.3.2.3 (Box 6, Folder 4.3)
      World War, 1914-1918; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; United States. Army. Officers -- History
  - Seventh Olympic Games, Antwerp (Belgium), 1920-1966; Subseries 3.3; 5 folders.
    Arranged chronologically. Contains clippings and serials some of which are written in French or Dutch.
    - Ons land in woord en beeld, 29 Augustus 1920; D394.3.3.1 (Box 6, Folder 5.1)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
    - Le Miroir des sports, 2 Septembre 1920; D394.3.3.2 (Box 6, Folder 5.2)
    - Sporting: Journal sportif illustré, 21 Septembre 1920; D394.3.3.3 (Box 6, Folder 5.3)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
    - Le miroir des sports, 30 Septembre 1920; D394.3.3.4 (Box 6, Folder 5.4)
    - Le miroir des sports, 14 Octobre 1920; D394.3.3.5 (Box 6, Folder 5.5)
    - Sporting: Journal sportive illustré, 12 Octobre 1920; D394.3.3.6 (Box 6, Folder 6.1)
    - Le Sportif, 9 Octobre 1920; D394.3.3.7 (Box 6, Folder 6.2)
    - Clippings, French rugby fans are keyed up for contest with Americans to-day, 1920; D394.3.3.8 (Box 6, Folder 7.1)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
    - Clipping, Amerique contre sud-est de la France, 1920; D394.3.3.9 (Box 6, Folder 7.2)
    - Clipping, American rugby team shows up weill in practice; Winners: American rugby team wihich will meet French on Sunday at Colombes, October 8, 1920; D394.3.3.10 (Box 6, Folder 7.3)
      Orignal and copy.
    - Clipping, Les Californiens vont-ils continuer à vaincre?, 1920; D394.3.3.11 (Box 6, Folder 7.4)
    - Clipping, Un team redoutable et redoute: l'equipe Americaine de Californie, 1920; D394.3.3.12 (Box 6, Folder 7.5)
    - Clipping, Californiens contre selection du Sud-Ouest: en lever de rideau Sectionnistes contre Hendayais, 1920; D394.3.3.13 (Box 6, Folder 7.6)
    - Clipping, Un match international de rugby: après une ardente bataille, les Californiens ont battu l'equipe du Sud-Ouest par 6 points a 3, 1920; D394.3.3.14 (Box 6, Folder 7.7)
    - Clipping, Un beau debut de la saison de rugby les Californiens vont se heurter a une Selection du Sud-Est, 1920; D394.3.3.15 (Box 6, Folder 7.8)
    - Clipping, Match international la Californie bat le Sud-Ouest par 6 points (2 essais) a 3 points (1 essai), 4 Octobre 1920; D394.3.3.16 (Box 6, Folder 7.9)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E.; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
    - Clipping, Les Americains battent les Toulousains par 11 points a 3, 1920; D394.3.3.17 (Box 6, Folder 7.10)
    - Clipping, International rugby: French team beats the U.S. by 14 points to 5, 1920; D394.3.3.18 (Box 6, Folder 7.11)
    - Clipping, Rugby too brutal for soldiers, say French officers, 1920; D394.3.3.19 (Box 6, Folder 7.12)
      Rugby football; Violence in sports; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
    - Clipping, Les rugbymen Americains vaincront-ils l'equipe de France?, 1920; D394.3.3.20 (Box 6, Folder 7.13)
    - Clipping, Americans hopeful of beating France, 1920; D394.3.3.21 (Box 6, Folder 7.14)
    - Clipping, How many of these, February 23, 1949; D394.3.3.22 (Box 6, Folder 7.15)
      Article inscribed to Babe Slater
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
    - Clipping, Tense moment in the international rugby match between Pan-American and Pan-French olympic teams, October 31, 1920; D394.3.3.23 (Box 6, Folder 7.16)
    - Clipping, Sporting: Rugby, 1920; D394.3.3.24 (Box 6, Folder 7.17)
    - L'Athelete: journal hebdomadaire de tous les sports, 2 Octobre 1920; D394.3.3.25 (Box 6, Folder 7.18)
    - Le Progress: journal republicain quotidien, 20 Septembre 1920; D394.3.3.26 (Box 6, Folder 7.19)
    - Le Midi sportif, 24 Septembre 1920; D394.3.3.27 (Box 6, Folder 7.20)
    - Report of the American Olympic Committee: Seventh Olympic Games, Antwerp, Belgium, 1920, 1921; D394.3.3.28 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      The followint pages of the Report of the American Olympic Committee (1920) were marked with post-it notes: pages 1, 15, 19, 23, 24, 29, 137.
      Rugby football; Sports -- History -- 20th century; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
    - Photocopies, Winners in a foreign game: rugby football, 1921; D394.3.3.29 (Box 1, Folder 24 A)
      Photocopy of article from: Report of the American Olympic Committee, Seventh Olympic Games, 1920.
      Rugby football teams -- United States; Rugby football; Sports -- History -- 20th century; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
    - Photocopies, Gold medal won by United States Olympic games rugby team in Antwerp (Rugby USA, v.1 no.1), May 1966; D394.3.3.30 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Original photocopy and copy.
      Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Sports -- History -- 20th century; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
  - Eighth Olympic Games, Paris, 1924-2004; Subseries 3.4; 2 folders.
    Contains clippings. See also the Scrapbook series for additional clippings.
    - Clipping, "Friendship Fund,", March 11, 1924.; D394.3.4.1 (Box 6, Folder 8.1)
    - Clipping, What becomes of old athletes?--an answer, June 3, 1951; D394.3.4.2 (Box 6, Folder 8.2)
      Three copies. Two copies in manilla envelope within smaller folder.
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Hyland fling, March 29, 1950; D394.3.4.3 (Box 6, Folder 8.3)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archives; O'Neil, John T. (John Thomas), 1898-1950; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Hyland, Dick
    - Clipping, Pocketbooks, pantry shelves face controls, October 18, 1950; D394.3.4.4 (Box 6, Folder 8.4)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archives; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Valentine, Alan Chester, 1901-
    - Clippings, Again annex Olympic games rugby title, 1924; D394.3.4.5 (Box 6, Folder 8.5)
      small piece of article detatched.
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archives; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, 50 years ago--1924, April 16, 1974; D394.3.4.6 (Box 6, Folder 8.6)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archives
    - Clipping, Rugby's still the game of '24 Olympic winner, undated; D394.3.4.7 (Box 6, Folder 8.7)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Old memories rehashed as past Olympians fete Brutus Hamilton, April 11, 1952; D394.3.4.8 (Box 6, Folder 8.8)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Hamilton, Brutus, 1900-1970; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clippings, The Administration: for an old rugby player, October 16, 1950; D394.3.4.9 (Box 6, Folder 8.9)
      Two pages.
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Valentine, Alan Chester, 1901-; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Sports: Woodland Daily Democrat, March 10, 1924; D394.3.4.10 (Box 6, Folder 8.10)
    - Clipping, Hyland fling, February 4, 1951; D394.3.4.11 (Box 6, Folder 8.11)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Hyland, Dick
    - Clipping, Great rugby upset in 1924 Olympics, undated; D394.3.4.12 (Box 6, Folder 8.12)
    - Clipping, A war tragedy, undated; D394.3.4.13 (Box 6, Folder 8.13)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Farish, Linn M. (Linn Markley ), 1901-1944
    - Clipping, Sport writers hail Linn Farish: DeGroot played with U.S. champs, undated; D394.3.4.14 (Box 6, Folder 8.14)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Farish, Linn M. (Linn Markley ), 1901-1944; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Valentine for Rochester, undated; D394.3.4.15 (Box 6, Folder 8.15)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Valentine, Alan Chester, 1901-; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clippings, Wallabies score 37-0 rugby win, undated; D394.3.4.16 (Box 6, Folder 8.16)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Hyland, Dick; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Hyland fling, April 24, 1953; D394.3.4.17 (Box 6, Folder 8.17)
      Rugby football; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Hyland, Dick
    - Clipping, Farish great hero of war, undated; D394.3.4.18 (Box 6, Folder 8.18)
    - Clipping, Good old rugby, December 12, 1959; D394.3.4.19 (Box 6, Folder 8.19)
    - Clipping, Linn Farish, Slaters rugby stars in 1924, undated; D394.3.4.20 (Box 6, Folder 8.20)
    - Clipping, How many do you know?, undated; D394.3.4.21 (Box 6, Folder 8.21)
    - Clipping, 25 years ago, undated; D394.3.4.22 (Box 6, Folder 8.22)
    - Clipping, 50 years ago--1924, April 10, 1974; D394.3.4.23 (Box 6, Folder 8.23)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979; Farish, Linn M. (Linn Markley ), 1901-1944
    - Clipping, 50 years ago--1924, May 20, 1974; D394.3.4.24 (Box 6, Folder 8.24)
    - Clipping, 50 years ago--1926, January 2, 1976; D394.3.4.25 (Box 6, Folder 8.25)
    - Clipping, Top 100 (Sacramento Bee sports section), November 23, 2001; D394.3.4.26 (Box 6, Folder 8.26)
      Slater, Colby E. -- Archive
    - Clipping, Many were star athletes in two sports (Sacramento Bee sports section), November 23, 2001; D394.3.4.27 (Box 6, Folder 8.27)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football teams -- United States; Sports -- History -- 20th century; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Banker who kept most precious gold at home, August 12, 2004; D394.3.4.28 (Box 6, Folder 8.29)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Rockefeller, James S., 1902-2004; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Innocents abroad, undated; D394.3.4.29 (Box 6, Folder 8.30)
      Handwritten note signed Mari (Babe Slater's daughter) attached to clipping addresses the question of whether Babe Slater is in the photograph and if 7th or 8th Olympic games.
    - Clipping, Teammates in the international Olympic games of 23 years ago met on the recent statewide tour of the Flying Farmers, Inc. of California, undated; D394.3.4.30 (Box 6, Folder 8.31)
    - Clipping, Farish rated with legendary figures, undated; D394.3.4.31 (Box 6, Folder 8.32)
    - Hyland fling, April 20, 1953; D394.3.4.32 (Box 6, Folder 8.33)
    - Hyland fling, April 28, 1953; D394.3.4.33 (Box 6, Folder 8.34)
    - Hyland fling, March 7, 1948; D394.3.4.34 (Box 6, Folder 8.35)
    - Hyland fling, March 13, 1948; D394.3.4.35 (Box 6, Folder 8.36)
    - Clippings, Stanford greats in Woodland: De Groot, Cleveland honor Linn Farish, January 4, 1945; D394.3.4.36 (Box 6, Folder 8.37)
    - Clipping, Immortal 'Babe' in Hall of Fame, June 12, 1973; D394.3.4.37 (Box 6, Folder 8.38)
    - Clipping, Aussies vie today in rugby battle, March 14, 1948; D394.3.4.38 (Box 6, Folder 8.39)
    - Clipping, San Francisco: nine o'clock news: the late Lieutenant Colonel Linn Farish, whose death was in an airplane accident September 10 was recently announced, undated; D394.3.4.39 (Box 6, Folder 8.40)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Farish, Linn M. (Linn Markley ), 1901-1944; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Skyscraper passes may prove undoing for McColl, undated; D394.3.4.40 (Box 6, Folder 8.41)
      Sports -- History -- 20th century; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; McColl, William F.
    - Clipping, 50 years ago--1924, March 26, 1974; D394.3.4.41 (Box 6, Folder 8.42)
    - Clippings, Sports: our team (the Daily Democrat), October 25, 1965; D394.3.4.42 (Box 6, Folder 8.43)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Burnett, Olive
    - Clipping, Sportscripts, undated; D394.3.4.43 (Box 6, Folder 8.44)
    - Clippings, Olympic rugby champions beat varsity on Christmas Day, undated; D394.3.4.44 (Box 6, Folder 9.1)
    - Clippings, Olympic rugby champions given 3-0 beating by Vancouver Rep fifteen, December 29, 1924; D394.3.4.45 (Box 6, Folder 9.2)
    - Clipping, Record crowd sees California win final, undated; D394.3.4.46 (Box 6, Folder 9.3)
    - Clipping, Olympic rugbyists triumph over U.B.C. in fast exhibition, 1924; D394.3.4.47 (Box 6, Folder 9.4)
    - Clipping, Mainland all stars defeated: American rugbyists excel in backfield play in 15 to 0 win, undated; D394.3.4.48 (Box 6, Folder 9.5)
      Olympic athletes -- United States; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Arciive; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Room for advance in rugby, undated; D394.3.4.49 (Box 6, Folder 9.6)
    - Clipping, Star attraction: Morris Kirksey, famous 100 and 220 yard dash man of California who is one of the aces of the visiting Olympic Rugby Club of California, undated; D394.3.4.50 (Box 6, Folder 9.7)
      Sports -- History -- 20th century; Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Olympic athletes -- United States; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive; Kirksey, Morris
    - Clipping, 50 years ago--1924, May 28, 1974; D394.3.4.51 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Clipping, This Is Your Chance To Honor A True Sportsman, Babe Slater, March 6, [1924]; D394.3.4.52 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Woodland (Calif.) -- History; Slater, Colby E.
  - Travel, 1913, undated; Subseries 3.5; 6 folders.
    Contains guides and other items related to travel in Belgium, France, Germany, and Switzerland.
    - Wiesbaden Official Guide: Information Respecting Baths and Treatment. Wiesbaden (Germany): Municipal Enquiry Office, 1913; D394.3.5.1; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Wiebaden (Germany) -- Description and travel; Health resorts -- Germany -- Wiesbaden; Hot Springs -- Germany -- Wiesbaden; Slater, Colby E. -- Archive